我们买了纸巾吗?
Did we get paper toweIs?
你是指我们打算 去店里买的东西吗?
You mean the thing we went to the store for?
没有
Nope.
我帮你们准备了一份礼物
Hey, I got you a present!
天啊,你把它藏在哪里?
Oh, my goodness, where did you hide it?
我订了它当做你们结婚的礼物 它终于送来了
I ordered it for your wedding and it's finaIIy here!
你不必送我们任何…
You didn't have to get us anything--
我喜欢它,它很大,我们打开它吧
I Iove it! It's huge! Let's open it!
-是小精灵的电动 -我的天啊
-It's a Ms. Pac-Man machine! -Oh, my God!
我不知道该把它放到哪里去
I didn't know where to put it.
-我们可以把它放在客房 -好吧
-We can put it in the guest bedroom. -Yeah, okay.
我喜欢把它放在这里
I kind of Iike it here.
你喜欢它吗?
Do you Iike it?
我小时候 都待在游乐场里
I practicaIIy spent my entire chiIdhood at the arcade.
-这是我第二喜欢的游戏 -你最喜欢什么?
-This was my second favorite. -What's your first?
-我记不得它的名字了 -它的内容是什么?
-I don't remember the name. -WeII, what did it do?
把铜板放进去 一拉把手,就能拿到糖果
You'd put a quarter in, puII some handIes and win a candy bar.
自动贩卖机?
A vending machine?
别为我难过 每次我都会赢
Don't feeI bad for me. I won every time!
片名:六人行 乔伊跟瑞秋约会
我很高兴你们都在
I'm so gIad you guys are here.
猜猜古生物系 发生了什么事
Guess what happened in the paIeontoIogy department.
你觉得他看到了我们 还有我们有机会落跑?
Do you think he saw us, or can we stiII sIip out?
系主任诺曼教授 要退休了,所以…
Professor Newman, the department head, is retiring, so....
-他们让你当系主任 -我要教他的高级课
-They made you head of the department! -I'm teaching his advanced cIass!
我为什么没有当上系主任?
Why didn't I get head of the department?
太棒了 你一直想教高级课
Great. You've aIways wanted to teach an advanced cIass.
不,我知道,它真的很棒 这是我一直在期待的机会
No, I know. It's reaIIy exciting. This is the break I've been waiting for.
制片:温蒂诺勒
我相信强制抗过敏排毒计画…
I'm not sure a court-ordered detox program...
编剧:雪瑞比尔星葛拉罕 艾伦普勒马
...was the break Professor Newman was waiting for.
不是诺曼教授 在等待的机会
但是…
But, hey.
瑞秋,我有个重要约会 你知道哪家餐厅不错吗?
Hey, Rach, I got a big date. Do you know a good restaurant?
导演:大卫修蒙
保罗咖啡厅,那里东西好吃 气氛真的很浪漫
PauI's Cafe. It's got great food and it's reaIIy romantic.
太棒了,谢谢
Great, thanks.
带她到四季饭店喝东西
Then take her to the Four Seasons for drinks.
或是到城里听爵士乐
Or go downtown and Iisten to some jazz.
或跳舞,带她去跳舞
Or dancing. Oh, take her dancing!
你真的很会拖延性爱游戏
You sure are naming a Iot of ways to postpone sex.
我想念约会的感觉 盛装打扮去好餐厅吃饭
I miss dating. Dressing up, going to a fancy restaurant.
我很久都无法再那么做了 那真的很有趣
I won't be abIe to do that for so Iong. And it's so much fun.
我不是说坐在这里 担心生产的事不好玩
Not that sitting around worrying about giving birth isn't fun.
知道吗?我们为什么不去约会?
Hey, you know what? Why don't I take you out.
你不想跟孕妇约会
You don't want to date a pregnant Iady.
我想我们会玩得很开心
Yes, I do. We're gonna have a good time.
我会让你忘了生孩子剖腹生产…
I'II take your mind off of chiIdbirth, and C-sections...
宝宝的头扩大了…
...and baby heads stretching out--
好吧,我答应你
Okay, I'II go with you.
-那会很好玩的 -好吧
-It wiII be fun. -AII right.
不,太棒了
No, no! Yes!
快来看
WouId you Iook at that.
我打败了你的最佳成绩 太惨了
I knocked off aII your top scores. How sad.
好吧,轮到我了
Okay, I'm next.
别再开始 轮到我了,菲比
Don't start another game. I'm next! Phoebe?
抱歉,我赢得太开心 听不到你说话
Sorry, I couIdn't hear you over aII the winning.
-菲比在霸占游戏 -那是个愚蠢的游戏
-Phoebe's hogging the game. -It's a stupid game.
你觉得它蠢 因为你很逊
You think it's stupid because you suck.
我不逊,它才逊
I don't suck. It sucks.
你很逊
You suck.
如果这游戏会引起你们的困扰 我应该留下它
If this game is gonna cause probIems, I shouId keep it.
不,我喜欢它,它是很棒的礼物
No, I Iove it. It is a great present.
你为什么不回家等谢卡呢?
Why don't you go home and wait for the thank-you card?
-你为什么要玩这个游戏? -它不会吐出糖果
-Why do you want to pIay this game? -It doesn't spit out a CIark Bar.
好吧,菲比,够了 快下来
Okay. Phoebe, that's it. Out of the chair.
菲比,钱德
Phoebe! ChandIer!
不,这是女孩的战争 我希望你们能互敬互爱
No, no. This is a girI fight. I'm hoping it wiII turn into Iove-pIay.
好吧,听着 我很抱歉…
Okay, Iook. Honey, I'm sorry...
我太凶了,我不是故意的 我真的很喜欢这个游戏…
...I'm acting hostiIe. I don't mean to. It's just that I Iove this game so much...
我也想玩玩它
...that I wouId just Iike the chance to pIay it too.
太神奇了,你在我耳边 像吉娃娃一样叫个不停…
Wow, it's amazing how weII I can pIay with you yapping around my head...
我还是能玩
...Iike a Chihuahua.
好吧,我受够了,钱德 帮我把她拉下来
AII right, that's it. ChandIer, heIp me get her out of the chair.
钱德,快点
ChandIer, come on.
乔伊,麻烦你去开门
Joey, couId you get that?
乔伊
Joey.
你这是干嘛? 我以为你在房里
I thought you were in your room.
我是来接你的 这是送你的
I'm picking you up for our date. For you.
百合花,它们是我最喜欢的花 谢谢
LiIies. They're my favorite. Thank you.
还有蛋糕
And a brownie.
只有一半
WeII, haIf a brownie.
事实上它只剩袋子
ActuaIIy, it's just a bag.
从花店走回来真的很远 我觉得头晕,所以…
It's a Iong waIk from the fIower shop and I feIt faint, so....
这真的是太棒了 我觉得好像真的在约会
This is so great! I actuaIIy feeI Iike I'm on a reaI date.
但我会害喜 我穿的内裤裤头高到…
But I have morning sickness and I have on underwear that goes up to...
这里
...there.
少来了,这是真的约会
Hey, come on. This is a reaI date.
你家好漂亮
So nice pIace you got here.
桌上足球,披萨盒
FoosbaII. Pizza box.
还有花花公子杂志 你是我喜欢的那种女人
Oh, a subscription to Playboy. My kind of woman.
那是我室友的杂志
That's my roommate's.
我想见见他 他似乎是个好男人
I'd Iike to meet him. He sounds Iike a standup guy.
他很保护我 你最好小心一点
He's protective of me, so you'd better watch yourseIf.
你室友很帅吗?
Your roommate, is he good-Iooking?
你一定很努力控制自己 不爱上他
Must be tough to keep your hands off him.
我相信他是男同志
I'm pretty sure he's gay.
不是的 你为什么要毁了这个游戏?
No! No, he's not! Why are you trying to ruin the game?
这让我想起葛瑞利的骨牌理论
Which brings us back to GreeIy's Theory of Dominance.
今天到此为止
That's it for today.
有人知道费利曼楼在哪里吗?
Does anyone know where the Freeman BuiIding is?
那是A大道的新大楼
It's the new buiIding on Avenue A.
它在城里的另一边 我10分钟内得赶到那里上课
That's across town. I'm teaching there in 1 0 minutes.
那是不可能的
Dude, that's not gonna happen.
快闪开
Move it! Move it!
我是老师
Hey! I'm the teacher!
哈
HeIIo.
抱歉我迟到了 我严重迟到
Sorry I'm a IittIe Iate. Whoa, a Iot Iate.
我从自我介绍开始吧
WeII, Iet me start by introducing myseIf.
我是盖勒教授
I'm Professor GeIIer.
总而言之…
So to sum up...
我是盖勒教授 今天大家做得很好
...I'm Professor GeIIer. Good job today.
-菲力牛排搭配什么? -蒸蔬菜
-What comes with the fiIet mignon? -Steamed vegetabIes.
除了蔬菜…
Instead of the vegetabIes...
我可以用什么东西搭配…
...is there any way that I couId substitute the...
三磅的龙虾?
...three-pound Iobster?
知道吗?帮她把两道菜都送上来
You know what? Bring her both.
我要点跟她一样的东西
And I'II have the same.
这真的是个很棒的约会
Wow, this is shaping up to be a pretty good date.
我差点忘了 我没给你房租
I aImost forgot. I didn't pay you the rent.
别当我们是室友,我们在约会
No roommate stuff. It's a date.
我想知道乔伊崔比亚尼 怎么跟女人约会
Wow, so I get to see what Joey Tribbiani is Iike on a date.
你有什么招数?
Have any moves?
不,我只会做我自己 如果她们不喜欢我…
No, I'm just myseIf, and if they don't Iike me for--
抱歉 我无法想像那种事
I'm sorry, I couIdn't even get through that.
我就知道,告诉我你有什么招数
I knew it. TeII me your moves.
好吧
AII right.
嗯…
WeII....
我会假装有影迷送一瓶红酒给我们
I start by having a bottIe of wine sent to my tabIe from a fan.
天啊,有用吗?
Oh, my God. And that works?
你得加上“这真是太不好意思了 我只想过正常人的生活”
If you add, ''This is embarrassing. I just want to have a normaI Iife.''
你们这些可怜的名人
You poor IittIe famous man.
好吧,这个呢?
Okay, how about this one?
我本来想等到送你回家再吻你…
I was gonna wait untiI the end of the night to kiss you...
但你真的太美了 我想我做不到
...but you're just so beautifuI, I don't think I can.
天啊
Oh, my God!
那真的太棒了 我差点就被你骗了
Wow, that was fantastic! I aImost Ieaned in. ReaIIy.
告诉我你用的是什么招数
So teII me one of your moves.
好吧
AII right.
你是在哪里长大的?
So where'd you grow up?
那就是你的招数?
That's your move?
瑞秋,还好你长得很美
Boy, Rach, you're Iucky you're hot.
-快回答我的问题 -皇后区
-Come on, just answer the question. -Queens.
你跟父母亲近吗?
Were you cIose to your parents?
-我跟妈妈亲,跟爸爸不太说话 -为什么?
-With my mom. Not so much my dad. -Why not?
我不知道 我们之间有距离
I don't know. There's just this distance.
我们都假装没有 但事实上不然
We both try to pretend it's not there, but it is.
那一定很辛苦
It's gotta be rough.
对,那真的很辛苦 有时候我认为…
Yeah, it's reaIIy tough. Sometimes I think....
哇
Wow!
太帅了
Nice move!
-“你在哪里长大的?”,太简单了 -谢谢
-''Where'd you grow up?'' So simpIe. -Thank you.
对不起,我要去洗手间
Now, excuse me. I'm gonna use the restroom.
-你正看着我走开 -没错,太简单了
-Now you're watching me waIk away. -Yes, I am! So simpIe!
-你一定不相信今天我做了什么 -很明显地你没洗澡或刮胡子
-You won't beIieve what I did today. -CIearIy not shower or shave.
我玩了这玩意一整天 现在我是第一名
I pIayed this aII day, and now I ruIe.
他们应该把它改名为 “钱德小姐”
They shouId change the name to ''Ms. ChandIer.''
还是不要好了
AIthough, I hope they don't.
你待在家里玩小精灵 我出门像牛一样在工作?
You stayed home and pIayed Ms. Pac-Man whiIe I went to work Iike a chump?
我包办了前10名 把菲比给挤掉了,庆祝一下吧
I got the top 1 0 scores. I erased Phoebe off the board. High-five!
你的手是怎么了?
What is the matter with your hand?
我打了八小时的电动
I pIayed for eight hours.
它会放松的,看看我的记录
It'II Ioosen up. Check out the scores.
看看我编的名字 它们全是脏话
AIso, Iook at the initiaIs. They're dirty words.
-钱德,你为什么要那么做? -因为它很棒
-ChandIer, why wouId you do that? -Because it's awesome.
你觉得那么做很聪明?
You think it's cIever?
我只能写下三个字母 除了屁股外,其他的名字可是个大挑战
They onIy give you three Ietters, so after A-S-S, it is a chaIIenge.
但你全都想出来了
But cIearIy you're up to the task.
-这不是脏话 -把它跟那个连在一起
-This one's not dirty. -Put it together with that one.
喔
Oh.
如果你没办法把它清掉 我不会答应你的
If you don't cIear this off, you won't get one of those from me.
班明天会过来 不能让他看到这个
Ben's coming over tomorrow. This can't be there.
-他不知道它们的意思 -他七岁了,他不笨
-He won't know what they mean. -He's 7, not stupid.
-最近你跟他谈过吗? -我要把＝插头拔掉
-Have you taIked to him IateIy? -I'm gonna unpIug it.
我没办法证明我今天做了什么 就跟我的工作一样
I'II have nothing to show for my day. Like work.
不
No!
你看,画面还在
Hey, Iook! It's stiII there!
这玩意一定是用 原始的记忆晶片
This thing must have some kind of primitive ROM chip!
你会说脏话 又懂电脑
Wow. The dirty words and the computer taIk.
这是你做过最酷的事
This is just the cooIest you've ever been.
-你得打败自己的成绩 -我的手指都张不开了
-You gotta beat your scores. -With the cIaw?
好吧,让我来 我们得把这个消掉
Fine, I'II do it. We gotta get this off.
卡萝还在气 你教他“拉我的手指”
CaroI's stiII upset that you taught him ''PuII my finger.''
拉我的手指,我的手毁了
PuII my finger. My hand is messed up!
-我不会回答那个问题 -来吧,快挑一个
-I am not gonna answer that. -Oh, come on. Just pick one.
在摩妮卡,菲比 钱德跟罗斯之间…
Between Monica, Phoebe, ChandIer and Ross...
如果你非那么做不可 你会打谁?
...if you had to, who wouId you punch?
我们是朋友,我不会打他们
We're friends. I wouIdn't punch any of them.
钱德吗?
ChandIer?
对,但我不知道为什么
Yeah, but I don't know why.
-我玩得很开心 -我也是
-I'm having a wonderfuI time! -Me too!
-这是我最棒的约会经验 -我知道
-This is the best date I ever had. -I know!
我笑得好厉害 你看到酒从我鼻子喷出来吗?
I Iaughed so hard. Did you see the wine come out my nose?
乔伊,我想大家都看到了
Joey, I think everybody saw it.
我不知道我会这么喜欢 没有性爱的约会
I never knew I couId enjoy the non-sex part of a date so much.
那是因为 你没有跟我约会过
That's because you have never been on a date with me before.
好吧,别批评我
AII right. Now don't judge me.
通常我会等我的对象离开了再这么做 但我真的饿坏了
I normaIIy wait tiII my date Ieaves, but I'm ripping into the swan.
好吧,你也别批评我
Okay, then you don't judge me.
我要去舔蛋糕的包装纸
I'm gonna suck on the ceIIophane from that brownie.
对
Oh, yeah.
告诉我乔伊崔比亚尼 说晚安的招数是什么
So teII me, what are Joey Tribbiani's end-of-the-night moves?
如果我要那个女孩吻我…
WeII, if I want the girI to kiss me...
首先我会让我的嘴巴 看起来难以抵抗
...first, I make my Iips Iook irresistibIe.
你都是怎么做的?
How do you do it?
你不能告诉任何人,但是…
Now you can't teII anyone, but...
我会涂上护唇膏
...I put on shiny Iip baIm.
-天啊 -女人就跟飞蛾扑火一样
-Oh, my God. -Like a moth to a fIame, I teII you.
-好吧,轮到你了 -不,我不想告诉你
-Okay, now you go. -No, I don't want to teII you.
-为什么? -那太丢脸了
-Why not? -It's embarrassing.
比涂覆盆子口味的护唇膏 还丢脸?
More embarrassing than shiny raspberry Iip baIm?
我刚刚没说覆盆子口味吧?
I didn't say raspberry before, did I?
快告诉我,瑞秋
Just teII me, Rach. Just teII me.
好吧
Okay.
站起来
AII right, stand up.
我们走到门边时…
WeII, when we're at the door...
我会将我的嘴唇 轻轻压在他的嘴唇上
...I IightIy press my Iips against his.
将身体靠向他 一秒钟
Then move into his body, just for a second.
然后我会发出这样的声音
And then I make this sound:
听起来没什么 但很有效
It doesn't sound Iike anything, but it works.
对,那的确有效
Oh, yeah. That wouId work, yeah.
好吧,我得睡了 我玩得很开心
AII right, I gotta go to bed. I had such a wonderfuI time.
我也是
Me too.
你迟到了50分钟? 你是用爬的吗?
You were 50 minutes Iate? Did you crawI?
不,我用跑的,那真的很远
No, I ran, okay? It's reaIIy far.
人们什么时候开始听不懂 “别挡我的路”?
When did peopIe stop understanding ''Get out of my way''?
你为什么不搭计程车?
Why didn't you take a cab?
塞车太严重,那是单行道 搭计程车得花两倍的时间
With the traffic and one-way streets, it'd take me twice as Iong.
我一星期有三堂课 我是洛克菲勒吗?
And I have cIass three times a week. Who am I, RockefeIIer?
你没办法再继续下去
You won't be abIe to keep doing this.
我不那么做 他们会取消我这堂课
If I don't, they'II take the cIass away from me.
我把它登在我家的通讯报上
And I put it in my famiIy newsIetter.
-什么? -你看过的,盖勒通讯报
-Your what? -You've seen it, The Geller Yeller.
对
Right. Wow.
我想出一条比较快的路线 我想这次我能及时赶到
I figured out a faster route. I'm sure I can make it this time.
我不能害怕 被车子撞到
I just can't be afraid to get a IittIe bit hit by cars.
-嘿 -嗨
-Hey. -Hi!
还记得我们谈过《狂犬惊魂记》吗?
Remember when we taIked about Cujo?
我不敢相信你没看过《狂犬惊魂记》
I can't beIieve you haven't seen Cujo.
别紧张,它不是《大国民》
ReIax, it isn't Citizen Kane.
你看完了《大国民》?
Have you ever sat through Citizen Kane?
对,它真的很无聊 但它是名片
Yeah, it's reaIIy boring. But it's, Iike, a big deaI.
总之,我想去租《狂犬惊魂记》
Anyway, I was thinking about renting Cujo.
我们今晚一起看吧
WeII, Iet's do it tonight.
-你不是有约会吗? -对
-Don't you have that big date? -Oh, right.
-乔伊,我能问你一件事吗? -问吧
-Hey, Joey, can I ask you something? -Yeah.
昨晚约会后你觉不觉得怪怪的?
After our date, did you feeI weird?
天啊,你也是吗? 我吓坏了,那是什么?
Oh, my God. You did too? It freaked me out. What was that?
我不知道 我想应该是龙虾的问题
I don't know. I'm kind of thinking it was the Iobster.
对,龙虾
Oh, yeah. Yeah, the Iobster.
-我吐了一整晚 -我也是
-I was up sick aII night. -Me too. AII night.
真的吗?我没看到你
ReaIIy? We didn't cross paths.
对,那是因为…
Yeah, weII, that's because...
我都待在房里
...I stayed in my room.
你不会想看我的洗衣篮的
You don't want to Iook in my hamper.
我懂了
Okay, I got that.
我要逃离那里 回到这里
I'II escape there. I'II come back here.
来吧,小精灵
AII right. Come on, Ms. Pac-Man.
你是个混蛋,对吧?
WeII, you're just a IittIe bitch, aren't you?!
大家好
Hey, you guys?
抱歉之前 我霸占着电动玩具
I'm sorry that I was hogging the game before.
如果你不快下来,我会杀了你
But if you don't get off soon, I wiII cut you.
天啊,你朋友名字的缩写真难听
Oh, my God! Your friends have some unfortunate initiaIs.
那都是钱德干的
They're aII ChandIer.
钱德不可能有这么厉害
ChandIer couIdn't get this good.
我很厉害,但那是要付出代价的
I did. But it came at a price.
班要过来,他不能看到这个
Ben's coming, and he can't see this.
七岁的孩子应该都看过杂交
By age 7, kids have aIready seen orgies.
还是只有我而已?
Was it just me?
总之…
So...
我们没时间了
...we're about out of time.
我知道我提供你们很多新资讯
Now, I know I've given you a Iot of new information.
那或许很吓人
And it may seem a IittIe overwheIming.
但今天…
But, if there's one thing...
在课堂上 你们得学会一件事…
...you need to take away from cIass today...
那就是…
...it's that...
恐龙永远都不会复活
...dinosaurs ain't never coming back.
下次再见
I'II see you next time.
我办到了,我及时赶到
Yes, I made it! I'm on time!
好了,请大家…
Okay, why don't we aII...
翻到第23页…
...open our books to page 23...
你们…
...where...
你们将会看到…
...where you wiII see...
很多红点
...a bunch of red spots.
请大家先看一下 我要…
Okay, why don't you aII start to read whiIe I....
这真的是太不好意思了
This is so embarrassing.
我只想过正常人的生活
I just want to have a normaI Iife.
那瓶红酒很贵的
Wow, that's an expensive bottIe of wine.
是吗?
It is?
真有趣 通常我的影迷不会那么做
That's funny, my fans don't normaIIy do that.
你没事吗? 你似乎有点心不在焉
Are you aII right? You seem a IittIe distracted.
不,我没事,我只是…
No, no, I'm fine. It's just....
我能问你一件事吗?
Hey, can I ask you something?
你有没有这样的经验 看着你认识的人…
Have you ever Iooked at someone you know...
突然间有不一样的感觉?
...and suddenIy seen them in a different way?
你是说从背后看吗?
You mean Iike from behind?
没错,就是那样
Yeah. That's exactIy it.
我从背后看这个家伙 觉得他真的很普通
I saw this guy from behind, and he seemed totaIIy normaI.
他一转身 我才知道他是史蒂芬鲍德温
And then he turned around and it was Stephen BaIdwin!
对
Yeah.
你完全了解我的意思
So you know exactIy what I mean.
没错
TotaIIy! Wow.
-对不起 -请便
-WouId you excuse me? -Sure.
-菲比,你真的很厉害 -我知道
-Phoebe! You're on fire! -I know!
你办得到
You can do it!
-别碰我 -别碰她
-Don't touch me! -Don't touch her!
左边,右边,右边
Go Ieft! Go right! Go right!
我办不到
I can't! I can't!
不,你这个天杀的…
No! You son of a--
菲比
Phoebe?!
嗨,班 不,别看机器
Oh, hi, Ben. No, don't Iook at the machine!
谢天谢地你回来了 我在看《狂犬惊魂记》
Thank God you're home! I'm watching Cujo.
-你一个人? -对,这只狗是怎么了?
-AIone? -Yes! What is wrong with this dog?
你看到库裘 自己去撞车的那一幕了吗?
Did you get to the part where Cujo throws himseIf at the car?
不,真的 这只狗是怎么了?
No, seriousIy, what's wrong with the dog?
等一下,你不是去约会了吗?
Wait, what happened to your date?
我们之间不来电
Oh, it didn't work out.
-你要跟我一起把电影看完吗? -好吧
-Want to watch the rest of the movie? -Oh, okay. Yeah.
我没有想过我会这么说…
I never thought I'd say this...
但我希望这只狗死掉
...but I hope this dog dies.
你在做什么? 坐在这里保护我
What are you doing? Sit here. Protect me.
没问题,有何不可呢?
Oh. Sure, yeah. Why not?
好吧
Okay.
-那就是,那就是库裘 -我知道
-That's him, that's him! That's Cujo! -I know.
没事的
It's gonna be okay.
天啊,现在会怎么做? 我不敢看
Oh, my God. What's he gonna do now? I can't watch.
你怎么能看这个? 你不害怕吗?
How can you watch this? Aren't you scared?
我怕极了
Terrified.
大家都来了吗? 今天我提早到了
So is everybody here? I got here a IittIe earIy, myseIf.
开始上课吧
Let us begin.
海德罗恐龙 主要分布在两个地方
Now, the hadrosaurids have been unearthed in two main Iocations.
这里…
Here...
跟…
...and...
这里
...here.
至于水龙…
Now, as for the hydrosaurs....